Die is a thriller, mystery film directed by Dominic James.
Six people, each of them is on the road to self-destruction.
They wake up in cells in a surreal facility, without
knowing how they got there or why.
Lisa, played by Emily Hampshire.
Mark Murdock, played by Elias Koteas.
Jacob, played by John Pyper-Ferguson.
Sofia Valenti, played by Caterina Murino.
Diane Robinson, played by Patricia McKenzie.
Zach Emmett, played by Karl Pruner.
Die Hard is an American action film series and media franchise that
originated with Roderick Thorp's 1979 novel Nothing Lasts Forever.
All five films revolve around the main character of John McClane (Joe Leland in the original novel), a police detective who
continually finds himself in the middle of a crisis where he is both the only hope against disaster and the culprit's target.
Per the franchise's name, McClane confounds repeated attempts to kill him, driving
his enemies to distraction, by adding up and exploiting dumb luck.
The films have grossed a combined $1.4 billion worldwide, with Bruce
Willis as the only actor to appear in all five films.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.